Guide to the Records of the Women's Philharmonic M1470
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Records of the Women's Philharmonic,
1981-2004
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Women's Philharmonic
M1470
210 Linear Feet
174 box(es)
The Women's Philharmonic was a professional orchestra dedicated to the promotion of women composers and performers. The collections contains files related to all aspects of the organization including programs, business records, music library materials, correspondence, and more.
Scope and Contents
The Women's Philharmonic collection consists of mixed materials reflecting this organization's administrative and artistic lifespan which ranged from 1981 to 2004. A brief overview of this collection's contents includes: programs; photographs; biographical materials of composers, conductors and guest artists; orchestra personnel rosters; financial and grant records; fund raising activities; audience surveys and marketing efforts; concert production notes; correspondence which ranges from office memoranda to letters from Nan Washburn, Elizabeth Min, Miriam Abrams, JoAnn Falletta, Apo Hsu and others; music library materials and catalogs; female composer and conductor initiative materials such as the National Women's Composer Resource Center as well as press and reviews collected during its twenty-four year history.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Women's Philharmonic, 2005, accessions 2005-122 and 2005-209. Additional material transferred from the Music Library, 2007, accession 2007-020.
Music by women composers; Music -- Performance -- California -- San Francisco; Women's Philharmonic; Women's Philharmonic; Women's Philharmonic
- Series I: Concert Programs
  Scope and Contents
  Concert Programs are filed chronologically within boxes without folders.
  - Concert Programs, August 19, 1981 - May, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Concert Programs, June 14, 1996 - March 7, 2004 (Box 2)
- Series II: Artist Photographs
  Artist Photographs
  This includes professional headshots of guest artists, composers and conductors, promotional photos of the orchestra, informal photographs of instrumentalists and others associated with the Women's Philharmonic.
  - Artist Photographs: A-M (Box 3)
  - Artist Photographs: M-W (Box 4)
  - Apo Hsu photos (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Womens Philharmonic cello section (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Susan Wong photos (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Wu Han photos (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Eugenia Zuckerman photo (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Wu Man photo (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Womens Philharmonic (WP) Proof sheets (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - (3) women Photos (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Photos (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - WP Photos (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Photos for Newsletter (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - 1997-1998 season photos (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Who Are They? Misc. Photographs (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Organization and Artist photographs (Box 167)
  - Miscellaneous Organization and Artist photographs (Box 168)
  - Velvet Brown (Tuba) photo (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Kendra Colton (Soprano) photo (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Cindy Cox (Composer) photo (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Apo Hsu (Conductor) photo (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Joan Jeanrenaud (Cellist) photos and slides (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Sara Jobin (Conductor) photo (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Libby Larson (Composer) photos (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Artist and Conductor photos (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - Ursula Oppen (Pianist) photo (Box 167, Folder 9)
  - Jean Stapleton (Narrator) photos (Box 167, Folder 10)
  - Linda Tillery and Cultural Heritage Choir photo (Box 167, Folder 11)
  - Karen Tanaka (Composer) photo (Box 167, Folder 12)
  - Joan Tower (Composer) photo (Box 167, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous orchestra photos, 1995-1996 (Box 167, Folder 14)
  - Carolyn Harrell photo (Box 167, Folder 15)
  - Final Concert photographs, March 2004 (Box 167, Folder 16)
  - Final Concert photographs, March 2004 (Box 167, Folder 17)
  - Women's Philharmonic, March 2004 (Box 167, Folder 18)
  - New Music Reading, August 11, 2000: photographs (Box 167, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, n.d. (Box 167, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, n.d. (Box 167, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, n.d. (Box 167, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, n.d. (Box 167, Folder 23)
  - Sharon Beals, slides and negatives, 1987 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - JoAnn Faletta, photos (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Photo CD/slide (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - 2 photograph albums (Box 169)
  - Oversize Photographs of Orchestra; Concert Advertisement (Flat-box 173)
- Series III: Administration
  Administration
  This includes all materials relating to the office and its organization; job descriptions; website design; and correspondence relating to everyday tasks as well as from patrons; local arts organizations with whom the Women's Philharmonic may have had relationships with; legal counsel materials and miscellaneous in-office correspondences. Also included are merchandise materials and office materials.
  - Subseries I: Legal Counsel materials
    Legal
    This file contains legal support materials; copyright advice, artist contract samples and correspondence regarding a potential lawsuit concerning the Women's Philharmonic practice of hiring only of female musicians for the orchestra.
    - Clancy, Case and Associates (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Copyright Attorneys (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Women Only Orchestra Legal Notes (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Legal: Visa anti-trust settlement (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - 1994-95 Consultants (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Sample Contract (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Contracts (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Subseries II: Misc. Organizational Correspondence
    Misc. Organizational Correspondence
    This file contains memos and emails sent to and from office staff of the Women's Philharmonic. Job duties lists, office equipment needs and some office meeting notes are included.
    - Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence to be filed (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence from other Arts Organizations (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - General Info/Correspondence Community Women's Orchestra (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Letters to/from JoAnn Falletta (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Memos/ Pamela Wilson (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Misc. Inquiry Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Correspondence (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Recent Memos Summer 1999 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - MISC. Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - 1998 Misc. Office Notes and Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - 1989-90 Correspondance (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Blake Howard correspondence (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Pamela Wilson Job Duties list (2000 January - March) (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - 1 Unpaid office residency 2000/01 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Misc. office notes/memos (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Misc. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Unmarked folder: office materials (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Misc. (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - 2002 Feminism Conference (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Fall Asks (office items desired) (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Pulitzer Prize information materials (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Equal Rights Admendment information (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Office Correspondence (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - Office Correspondence and Materials 1988-2000 (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - Subseries III: Women's Philharmonic Merchandise materials
    Merchandise
    This includes order forms, orders filled and a listing of the various cds, cassettes or other items for sale.
    - Merchandise Order Forms FY 2004 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Order forms (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Merchandise Orders Filled (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Merchandise Inventory (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Merchandise Order Forms (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Merchandise Order forms-in house (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Concert Merchandise Agreements (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Merchandise (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - CD and Cassette List (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Florence Price (composer) (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Florence Price CD orders (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Subseries IV: Women's Philharmonic Office Materials
    Office Materials
    This includes website information, staff planning, tax forms, work planning, volunteer lists and other miscellaneous information pertaining to office staff and office operation.
    - Signature (for business check signing) (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - DSL First World (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Staff Planning (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Workplans 1999 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - MO Work (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Website (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Health Insurance (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Computers (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - 1997/98 Subs Work to do (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Logo stats (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Information and Referral Guide (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Job Notes from Heidi (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Check Requests (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Budget (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Info (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - 2001 Tax Forms (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Tax Forms (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Need Check/Signatures (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Misc. Organizational Materials (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Volunteers 1994-95 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Mailing Lists Purchases or Exchanges (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - World Wide Web Project/Resources (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Forms: Masters and extra copies (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Old Notepad sheets (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Misc. Interns/Vols. (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Bulk Mail Information/Rates (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Contact Infos (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Direct Mail (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - School Material (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Contract rework (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Recording Release (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - The Women's Philharmonic Rider for concert (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Web 11/1999 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Database (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - To file: Misc. Office Materials (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Bulk Mail--The Mail House (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Misc Resources (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Printers--Dharma (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Messenger Service (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Printer--The Envelope Company (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Forms-masters (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Forms (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Adobe Pagemaker (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - 1998 Membership Form (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Triplex-Mail List Rental (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Page Maker Customer Support (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Page Maker for Windows Help (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Print Avenue (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Media Alliance (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Misc. Office services (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Management Center (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Misc. Notes: office equipment (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Seller's permit (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - 1992 Misc. Office materials (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - 2003 Misc. Financial statements (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Info (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Tax ID Number letter (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - State of Oregon revenue filing letter (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Subseries V: Miscellaneous Administrative materials
    - Booking Inquiries and Leads (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Mentor (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - PM (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Returned Contracts (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Proclamation/Resolution "WP Day," 1/25/97 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - OLIS (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Long Beach Symphony (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Los Angeles Jewish Symphony (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Beijing Women's Philharmonic (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Arts and Other Organizations outreach (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Chanticleer (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Chanticleer (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Advocacy Examples (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Women's Music Orgs (other) (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Other Symphonies (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Polyrhthm Productions (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Schola Cantorum (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - S. F. Gay Men's Chorus (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Interesting contacts (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Community Women's Orchestra Programs (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - The Community Women's Orchestra (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - SF Symphony (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Aspen Music Festival, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - 1992 International Women's Brass Conference (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - New Englan Women's Symphony (Box 54, Folder 44)
    - 20th Century Forum (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Conferences/Events (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Competition (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - ASCAP Award 1993; Indie Award 1993 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Grawemeyer Music Award (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Guild/Auxillary (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Goethe Institute and Feminism Conference materials and correspondence (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Mannheim Orchestra (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Statistical data on women in orchestral music (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Computer file set-up notes (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Computer consulting 2000 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Website Updates (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Rental Space for Offices (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - 44 Page St. Lease (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - 44 page St. Landlord Lease (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Key agreements: 44 Page st. (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - 44 Page St. Suite Lease (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - 44 Page St: Jordan Real Estate (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Office Space notes (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Job Listings 2000 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - 1999 Calendar: Work Plan and Office Memos (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Administration materials and schedules (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Office procedures (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Work Plan 1999 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Volunteers for Office (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - Misc. Administrative tasks and notes (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Office notes (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Administrative contact list (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Internships (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Administrative tasks and correspondence, October 2001 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Staff letters and memos (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Office tasks, 1999 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Townsend - Lease (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Organizational Planning draft materials (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Gift certificates and subscriptions, 2000-2001 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - CBO Contract/correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Ticket sales, 1996-1997 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Women's Philharmonic at Stanford, 1984-1988 (Box 148)
    - General Administrative, 1994 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Boulanger Award (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Union, 1995-1996 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League statistical reports (1992-1993) (Box 150, Folder 19)
    - Bay Area Women's Philharmonic: prospectuses (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Bay Area Women's Philharmonic: prospectuses (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - "Women's Philharmonic Organizational Plan: July 1, 1990 - June 30, 1993" (Box 172, Folder 3)
- Series IV: Catalog of Composers
  Catalog
  This contains a list of female composers which was researched and developed by the Women's Philharmonic music librarian. One catalogue represents women composers from the Baroque era to the 1990s; a second catalogue pairs publishers with various female composers to aid with the acquisition of repertoire. Other catalogs included are an International catalog and a Black Women composers catalog.
  - Subseries I: Composers
    - Composers: Alexander - Bond (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Composers: Bonis - Cox (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Composers: Crawford-Seeger - French (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Composers: Galbraith - Janisse (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Composers: Karpmon - Lombardini-Sirmen (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Composers: Macauly - Musgrave (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Composers: Na - Sergei (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Composers: Ravel - Shatin (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Composers: Shore - Tailleferre (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Composers: Tan - Vogelsang (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Composers: Walker - Warshaw (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Composers: Watkins - Zwilich (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Composer/Publishers: Alter - Bond (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Composer/Publishers: Bonds - Chaminade (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Composer/Publishers: Chance - DuPage (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Composer/Publishers: Edwards - Hunkins (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Composer/Publishers: Ivey - Kubik (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Composer/Publishers: Labori - Lutyens (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Composer/Publishers: Maconchy - Musgrave (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Composer/Publishers: Nazirova - Perry (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Composer/Publishers: Pierce - Roger (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Composer/Publishers: Saliutrinskaya - Swicher (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Composer/Publishers: Talma - Wallach (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Composer/Publishers: Warren - Zwilech (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Misc. Publishers: A - Lo (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Misc. Publishers: Lu - Yb (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Black Women Composers (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Subseries II: International Composers
    - Benavente, Regina (Argentina) (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Dianda, Hilda (Argentina) (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Guerreno, Amanda (Argentian) (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Mell, Eidylia Rosa (Argentina) (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Kohan Descher, Celina (Argentina) (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Pera, Graciela (Argentina) (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Terzian, Alicia (Argentina) (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Rud, Diana (Argentina) (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Urteaga, Irma (Argentina) (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Uarela, Marta Ines (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Ventura de Buligovich, Rita (Argentina) (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Nova-Sondag, Jacqueline (Colombia) (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Potes, Alba Lucia (Colombia) (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Arismendi, Diana (Venezuela) (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Aretz, Isabel (Argentina, Venezuela) (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Astuni, Silvia (Argentina) (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Bringuer, Estela (Argentina) (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Cervantes, Maria (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Corona, Beatriz (Cuba) (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Lambertini, Marta (argentina) (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Leon, Tania (Cuba) (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Luengo, Maria Teresa (Argentina) (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Paraskevaidis, Graciela (Uruguay) (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Patino, Lucia (Ecuador) (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Peralta, Catalina (Colombia) (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Catalago de Musica Clasica...de Puerto Rico (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Villarini, Awilde (Puerto Rico) (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Fernandes, Maria Helena Rosas (Brazil) (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Rezende, Marisa (Brazil) (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Yampolschi, Roseane (Brazil) (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Alexander, Leni (Chile) (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Ortiz, Gabriela (Mexico) (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Paredes, Hilda (Mexico) (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Vazquez, Alida (Mexico) (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Vazquez, Lilia Kuntze (Mexico) (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Czech (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Germany (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Israel (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Japan (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - New Zealand (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - Norway (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - Latina Composers (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - African-American Women Composers (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Latin American Catalogue (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Series V: Development: Grants/Giving
  Grants and Foundations
  This series contains grants, corporate sponsorships, and donor foundations through which the Women's Philharmonic sought funding. Some of the grants included are the National Endowment for the Arts (NEA); Cultural Equity Grant (CEG); Grants for the Arts (GFTA); the San Francisco Arts Commission (SFAC) and Meet the Composer. Corporate sponsor inquires and correspondences are also included as are foundation awards and correspondences. Audit materials and box office materials (invoices, receipts, tickets sold, etc.) are also included.
  - Subseries I: Box Office Materials
    - Box Office Rcpts (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - 1990-91 Box Office Specs (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Box Office 1991-92 Season (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - 1993-94 Box Offices (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - 1994-95 Box Office (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - City Box Office Paperwork (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Reconciliation/$ Sent City Box Office (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Ticket Web (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Gala 10/16/1999 Ticket Register (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - 1996-1997 City Box Office (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - Ticket sales: "A Few Good Women" 1998 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - "A Few Good Women" Ticket Sales 1998 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - City Box Office 2000-20001 Contract (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - 1998-1999 City Box Office (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - 1998-1999 City Box Office Settlements (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - City Box Office: Grants for the Arts (GFTA) Financial Letter (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Herbst Rental Agreement 2000-2001 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - City Box Office Nov. 24, 2000 Box Office settlement (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - City Box Office: Sept. 30, 2000 Box office settlement (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - May 28, 1999 Complimentary tickets lists (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - 1999-2000 Season subscription materials (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - 1998-1999 Season subscription/seating/ticket information (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - 1997-1998 City Box office materials (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Ticket count 1998-1999 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - 1997-1998 Ticket sales results (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Ticket sales (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Year end ticket sales results: 1999 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Subseries II: California Arts Council
    - California Arts Council (CAC) (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - California Arts Council (CAC) Touring (old) (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - California Arts Council (CAC) (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - California Arts Council 84-85 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - California Arts Council 85-86 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - California Arts Council 86-87 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - CAC Multi-Residence (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - CAC status/cultural equity materials (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - CAC Challenge 1996-1997 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - CAC challenge 1989-1995 (Part I) (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - CAC challenge 1989-1995 (Part II) (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - CAC 1996-1997 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - CAC 1995-1996 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - CAC 1994-1995 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - CAC 1993-1994 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - CAC 1992-1993 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - CAC 1991-1992 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - CAC 1989-1990 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - CAC education partner 1998-1999 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - CAC Touring 1996-1998 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - CAC Touring 1998-2000 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - CAC Touring Guide 1993-1995 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - CAC Touring 1992 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - CAC Touring, 2002-2004 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - CAC Touring, 2000-2002 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - CAC 1997-1998 (2nd year report) (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - CAC Rural & Inner City Presentation Program (1999) (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - CAC Challenge, 1997-1998 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - CAC: Education Demonstration Project (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - CAC: OS (FY 2000) (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - CAC: OSP (FY 1999) (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - CAC: OSP, 1998-1999 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - CAC: Challenge Grant, 2000-2001 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - CAC: Artists Fellowship Program (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - CAC: Annual Reports (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - CAC: OSP, 2000-2001 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - CAC Challenge (FY 1999) (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - CAC Challenge (1998-1999) (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - CAC, 1999 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - CAC: American Disabilities Act compliance (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - CAC: 2nd year report (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - CAC: OSP, 2001-2002 report (Box 139, Folder 15)
    - CAC, Invoice 2000 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - California Arts Council (Box 147, Folder 3)